https://www.dualitysoft.com/privacy.html

Privacy Statement
Internet user privacy and confidentiality is of the utmost importance to Duality Software. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
Description of Information Collected and Usage
Unless the user provides it voluntarily, Duality Software does not collect any personally identifiable information about visitors to www.dualitysoft.com.
Some Duality Software pages permit visitors to request additional information. The information collected at these pages includes name, company name, and e-mail address. In addition, visitors are able to e-mail messages to Duality Software that will contain the user's screen name and e-mail address, as well as any additional information the user may wish to include in the message.
Duality Software uses the information visitors provide about themselves to fulfill those visitors' requests. Return e-mail addresses are used to answer messages received.
When you place an order online with us, we use third-party e-commerce services, provided by PayPro Global. You can access their privacy policies at PayPro Global privacy statement.We do NOT keep credit card information as part of your product registration.
We keep your name, email address, mailing address, and phone number in our database to send registration information to you.
Duality Software may use customer information to provide you with notices of new information that may be of use or interest to you. This may include notification on the availability of new products, product updates, maintenance releases, and beta versions of products.
Occasionally a customer may be asked to provide a statement, provide a reference, authorize a quote or testimonial, or participate in a press release or case study.
No customer is obligated to provide any details about the product or it's use. No statements will be taken or used without prior written consent of the individual making the statement AND his/her employers consent.
Policies Regarding Third Parties
Duality Software does not currently share, trade, rent, or sell the information collected from this site - or information provided to us by our customers through offline means - to any third parties. Duality Software does not have any plans to begin sharing, trading, renting, or selling any information about our customers or web site visitors to third parties.
Duality Software Privacy Policy Changes
If Duality Software decides to change its privacy policy, Duality Software will post these changes here. Please feel free to contact us if you have further questions regarding our privacy practices.
Copyright © 1998-2020 Duality Software. All rights reserved.
Contacts | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
